Indiana University President's Office records, 1962-1968 C304
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1962-1968
  - Student Organizations (Box 163)
    - OUR, YAF and others, 1965-1967 (Box 163)
      This file includes material related to the National Student Association (NSA), Organization for University Reform (OUR), Progressive Reform Party (PRP), Students for an Orderly Society (SOS), Young Americans for Freedom, and other student groups.
      Separated Material
      Clippings and correspondence related to Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) have been removed and filed under "Student Organizations- Students for a Democratic Society".
    - Registration, 1966-1968 (Box 163)
    - Sexual freedom league, 1967 (Box 163)
    - Students for a Democratic Society (Box 163)
      - October 1965-1966 (Box 163)
      - 1967-1970 (Box 163)
  - Student Personnel, Division of, annual report, 1962-1967; (4 folders) (Box 163)
  - Student Publications (Box 163)
    - 1965 (Box 163)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 163)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 163)
  - Student Records, 1966-1968 (Box 163)
  - Student Senate meeting, Distinguished alumni, 1965 (Box 163)
  - Student Visitations, 1966-1968 (Box 163)
  - Su, 1962-1968 (Box 163)
  - Sum, 1962-1968 (Box 163)
  - Summer sessions (Box 164)
    - Annual report, 1962-1968; (7 folders) (Box 164)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 164)
    - Study of Students in the 1961 intersession and post-session, 1964 (Box 164)
  - Summer sessions (Box 165)
    - Schedule, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 165)
    - "A comparison of academic achievement… Intersession 1963 with …, Spring Semester 1962-1963; 1956 (Box 165)
    - Statistics, 1962-1963 (Box 165)
  - SUTCC (Box 165)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968; (2 folders) (Box 165)
    - History, 1967 (Box 165)
    - Instructional material, 1967-1968 (Box 165)
    - Inventory, 1967-1968 (Box 165)
    - Medical instructional TV, 1967-1968 (Box 165)
    - Public television act of 1967 (Box 165)
    - Technical relations, 1965-1968 (Box 165)
  - Sutton, Joseph L. (Box 165)
    - 1964-1968, (5 folders) (Box 165)
    - Appointment as vice-president and dean of the faculties, 1966 (Box 165)
    - Checks received, 1966-1967; (2 folders) (Box 165)
    - Entertainment expenses for reimbursement fro the IU Foundation representation fund, 1966-1967 (Box 165)
    - Speeches, 1968 (Box 165)
  - Swe, 1962-1968 (Box 165)
  - Sw, 1962-1968 (Box 165)
  - Szabo Food Service, Inc., 1962-1963 (Box 165)
  - T, 1962-1968 (Box 165)
  - Task force on the public university and public affairs, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - Tax (Box 166)
    - 1966-1968, (5 folders) (Box 166)
    - Monroe county tax board controversy, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 166)
    - Proposals to allow tuition tax credit, 1964-1965 (Box 166)
  - Taylor, Joseph T., 1966-1968 (Box 166)
  - Te, 1962-1968 (Box 166)
  - Teacher education (Box 166)
    - Regional center for research and development in teacher education; cooperative programs and miscellaneous, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 166)
    - Com: Insite (Instructional systems in teacher education), 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - Teacher insurance and annuity association (Box 166)
    - 1962-1968, (6 folders) (Box 166)
    - Annual reports, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 166)
  - Teachers insurance and annuity association (Box 167)
    - College retirement equities fund, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 167)
  - Teachers (Box 167)
    - Teaching assistants, 1963-1964 (Box 167)
    - Teaching associates, 1964-1965 (Box 167)
  - Telephone services (Box 167)
    - Annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 167)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 167)
    - Statement of account, 1964-1965 (Box 167)
  - Television (Box 167)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 167)
    - Closed circuit, 1962-1963; 1966; (2 folders) (Box 167)
    - Committee on instructional, 1966 (Box 167)
  - Testing (Box 167)
    - Bureau of educational studies and testing, 1962-1968; (8 folders) (Box 167)
    - College foreign language testing, 1964-1965 (Box 167)
  - Texas, 1963-1967 (Box 167)
  - Thailand (Box 167)
    - ICA Contract, 1962-1963 (Box 167)
    - U.S. AID, report, 1962-1963 (Box 167)
    - Institution building, report, [1962] (Box 167)
    - Institution building, appendices, [1962] (Box 167)
  - Thailand, Thammaset University, public administration program, reports and papers, 1962-1965 (Box 168)
  - Th, 1964-1967 (Box 168)
  - THo, 1962-1968 (Box 168)
  - Thor, 1962-1968 (Box 168)
  - Three semester plan, 1961-1965; (4 folders) (Box 168)
  - Ti, 1962-1968 (Box 168)
  - Ticket office, annual report, 1963-1964; 1967-1968 (Box 168)
  - To, 1962-1968 (Box 168)
  - Toledo, University of, 1962 (Box 168)
  - Toscanini estate, 1968 (Box 168)
  - Tr, 1962-1968 (Box 168)
  - Transportation (Box 168)
    - Campus bus system, 1966-1968 (Box 168)
    - Regional campus truck service, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 168)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 168)
  - Travel (Box 168)
    - Brochures, announcements, etc, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 168)
    - Asia and Middle East trip made by Dean Sutton, July-Aug. 1967 (Box 168)
    - Documents, letters of introduction for I.U. representatives from Pres. Office, 1966-1968 (Box 168)
    - Requests, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 168)
  - Travel (Box 169)
    - President's office, 1962 (Box 169)
    - Study tours, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 169)
  - Treasurer's advisory council, 1965 (Box 169)
  - Treasurer's office (Box 169)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 169)
    - Information manual, 1964 (Box 169)
    - Annual report, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 169)
    - Regional campuses, minutes and business officers' meeting, 1966-1968 (Box 169)
    - Staff meeting, 1964-1968 (Box 169)
    - Office of the vice president and, annual report, 1962-1965; (5 folders) (Box 169)
  - Tri, 1966-1967 (Box 169)
  - Tu, 1962-1968 (Box 169)
  - Tulane University, 1966 (Box 169)
  - Tur, 1962-1968 (Box 170)
  - U, 1962-1968 (Box 170)
  - Un, 1962-1968 (Box 170)
  - Un, 1963 (Box 170)
  - Undergraduate development (Box 170)
    - 1963-1968, (5 folders) (Box 170)
    - Annual report, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 170)
  - Unionization (Box 170)
    - 1966-1968, (3 folders) (Box 170)
    - Labor relations, 1966-1968 (Box 170)
  - Unionization (Box 171)
    - Labor relations (Box 171)
      - 1966 (Box 171)
      - Dues check-off, 1966-1968 (Box 171)
    - Unions (Box 171)
      - 1967 (Box 171)
      - Dallas Sells, etc., 1965-1967; (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1964-1966, (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - Labor relations, 1955-1966; (2 folders) (Box 171)
    - 1962 (Box 171)
  - United fund (Box 171)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 171)
    - Citation to I.U. faculty and staff, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 171)
  - United Nations, 1961-1968; (5 folders) (Box 171)
  - United Negro College fund (Box 171)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 171)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 171)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 171)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 171)
    - General organization, 1962-1963 (Box 171)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 172)
    - Agency for international development (Box 172)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 172)
      - Survey, 1963 (Box 172)
    - Air force, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 172)
    - Army (Box 172)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 172)
      - Graduate program in Germany, 1963; (2 folders) (Box 172)
      - Selective service system, including classification advice cards, 1965-1966 (Box 172)
    - Atomic energy commission (Box 172)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 172)
      - Education and technology, 1963 (Box 172)
      - Fundamental nuclear energy, 1962 (Box 172)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 173)
    - Civil service commission (Box 173)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 173)
      - Federal agency – University conference, April 25-28, 1965 (Box 173)
    - Congress (Box 173)
      - Correspondence with legislators, 1964-1965v; (5 folders) (Box 173)
      - Economic opportunity act of 1964, 1964-1965 (Box 173)
      - Educational and research legislation (Box 173)
        - 1966-1968 (Box 173)
        - Public television act, 1967 (Box 173)
        - Student housing, 1967 (Box 173)
        - 1964-1966, (2 folders) (Box 173)
        - Higher education facilities act, 1963-1967; (3 folders) (Box 173)
        - International education act of 1966 (Box 173)
        - Technical services act, 1965-1966 (Box 173)
        - Higher education act of 1965 (Box 173)
        - College facilities bill; HEW appropriations; NDEA amendments, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 173)
      - Health care plans, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box 173)
      - National academy of foreign affairs, 1963-1964; (2 folders) (Box 173)
      - Reports, 1964; 1966; (2 folders) (Box 173)
      - Unemployment compensation legislation, 1966 (Box 173)
    - Department of agriculture, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 173)
    - Department of commerce, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 173)
    - Department of defense, 1963-1967; (4 folders) (Box 173)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 174)
    - Education, Office of (Box 174)
      - 1962-1968, (13 folders) (Box 174)
      - Survey of students enrolled for masters and higher degrees, 1964-1965; (2 folders) (Box 174)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 175)
    - Education, Office of (Box 175)
      - Economics of higher education, 1962 (Box 175)
      - Proposals for academic year Institute for Russian Teachers, 1961-1964 (Box 175)
      - Work study program, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Junior chamber of commerce, 1962-1963 (Box 175)
    - Saving and loan league, 1964 (Box 175)
    - Student aid fund, 1960-1968; (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - University club of Chicago, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 175)
    - Health, education, and welfare, Department of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 175)
    - Housing and home finance agency, 1963 (Box 175)
    - Housing and urban development, Department of, 1966-1968 (Box 175)
    - Information agency, 1963-1964; (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Interior, Department of, 1965-1968; (2 folders) (Box 175)
    - Justice, Department of, Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 175)
    - Labor, Department of, 1964-1968; (4 folders) (Box 175)
    - Military Academy, West point, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 175)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 176)
    - Navy, Department of the, 1963-1968; (5 folders) (Box 176)
    - Office of economic opportunity, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 176)
    - Post office, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 176)
    - President (Box 176)
      - Appointments, statements, reports, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 176)
      - Conference on education, 1965 (Box 176)
      - Meeting, 1964-1965 (Box 176)
      - 1964 (Box 176)
      - Committee on equal employment, 1962-1963 (Box 176)
    - Public health services (Box 176)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 176)
      - NIH heart program project committee, 1961-1965 (Box 176)
    - Science, Department of, proposed, 1962-1963 (Box 176)
    - Selective service commission (Box 176)
  - United States departments and agencies (Box 177)
    - State, department of, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 177)
    - Treasury, department of, Internal Revenue Service, 1962-1968 (Box 177)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 177)
    - Junior chamber of commerce, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 177)
  - University club, Faculty men's club, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 177)
  - University auditorium, annual report, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 177)
  - Auxiliary enterprises, 1967-1968 (Box 177)
  - University club, women's club, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 177)
  - University club of Indianapolis, 1965 (Box 177)
  - University club of New York, 1962 (Box 177)
  - University council (Box 177)
    - 1962-1968, (2 folders) (Box 177)
    - Vice president and treasurer, 1967-1971 (Box 177)
    - General maintenance contractors, 1967-1969 (Box 177)
    - In-house, 1964-1967 (Box 177)
    - University extension, Division of, annual report, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 177)
    - University press (Box 177)
      - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 177)
      - Annual report, 1962-1968; (3 folders) (Box 177)
      - Correspondence, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 177)
      - International affairs center publications, 1966-1968 (Box 177)
      - Letters and correspondence, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 177)
  - University press (Box 178)
    - Printed and mimeographed materials, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 178)
    - Operating statements, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 178)
    - Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 178)
    - The Academic Tradition, 1968 (Box 178)
  - University publications office, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 178)
  - University relations (Box 178)
    - Appointment books, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 178)
    - 1962-1968, (5 folders) (Box 178)
  - University re-organization, 1966-1968 (Box 178)
  - University school, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 178)
  - University schools (Box 179)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 179)
    - Handbook, 1967-1968 (Box 179)
    - Operating committee, policy committee, 1967-1968 (Box 179)
    - Annual report, 1965-1966 (Box 179)
    - Reports, 1962-1966; (4 folders) (Box 179)
    - Progress report on automation of records, 1965 (Box 179)
    - Study committee – Growth and change, 1966 (Box 179)
  - University theatre, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 179)
  - Upward Bound (Box 179)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 179)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 179)
  - Uralic – Altaic (Box 179)
    - 1962-1968, (7 folders) (Box 179)
    - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 179)
    - Proposed Finnish chair, 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 179)
  - Urban semester (Box 179)
    - Focus: the city, 1967-1968 (Box 179)
    - Programs, 1965-1966 (Box 179)
  - Uruguay (Box 179)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 179)
    - A.I.D. Contract, 1965-1966; (3 folders) (Box 179)
    - Uruguay Mechanical and electronic engineering education program, 1964-1966 (Box 179)
  - V, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Van, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Van Nuys, John D., 1962-1964 (Box 180)
  - Varsity Club, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Ve, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Venezuela (Box 180)
    - Catolica-Indiana (Venezuelan project), 1962-1965 (Box 180)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 180)
  - Veterans (Box 180)
    - 1966-1968 (Box 180)
    - Office of veterans affairs, 1926-1968; (2 folders) (Box 180)
  - Vi, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Vice president for graduate development and dean of the graduate school, annual report (Box 180)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 180)
  - Victorian studies (Box 180)
    - 1963-1964, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box 180)
    - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 180)
  - Vienna, University of, 1964-1965 (Box 180)
  - Viet-Nam (Box 180)
    - 1965-1967 (Box 180)
    - Demonstrations against Dow Chemical Company on campus, 1967 (Box 180)
    - Faculty-student demonstrations, 1966-1970 (Box 180)
    - Visit of Hon. Dean Rusk to I.U., 1967 (Box 180)
    - Faculty letters re Dow-Rusk demonstrations, 1967; (3 folders) (Box 180)
    - Vietnam perspective, CBS report, 1965 (Box 180)
  - Vincennes University, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 180)
  - Visher, S.S., 1962-1963 (Box 180)
  - Vo, 1962-1968; (2 folders) (Box 180)
  - Vocational education, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 180)
  - Wa, 1962 (Box 180)
  - Wabash valley interstate commission, 1965-1966 (Box 180)
  - Wag, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Wal, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Wall, 1962-1968 (Box 180)
  - Wallace, Governor George, 1963-1964 (Box 180)
  - Wallis, W. Allen; Commitment, concern, and apathy, National conference of Christians and Jews, 1967 (Box 181)
  - Wals, 1963 (Box 181)
  - War, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Was, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Wat, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Water resources research center (Box 181)
    - 1963-1967, (5 folders) (Box 181)
    - Annual report, 1963-1968; (4 folders) (Box 181)
    - "Federal-State Water Resources", 1968 (Box 181)
    - "Water Geology and the Future", 1967 (Box 181)
    - Proposal, undated (Box 181)
  - We, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Webs, 1965-1968 (Box 181)
  - Wei, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Weir, 1965-1966 (Box 181)
  - Weimer, Arthur M., 1962-1964; (2 folders) (Box 181)
  - Wel, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Wells, Herman B (Box 181)
    - 1961-1968, (7 folders) (Box 181)
    - Official entertainment, 1966-1968 (Box 181)
  - Welsh, Governor Matthew E., 1964-1965 (Box 181)
  - Wen, 1963-1967 (Box 181)
  - Wes, 1962-1968 (Box 181)
  - Wescoe, Clark; "Expansion and excellence: A choice in higher education?", 1965 (Box 181)
  - West Baden Project (Box 182)
    - Final report and feasibility study, 1967 (Box 182)
    - Consultants, 1965-1966 (Box 182)
    - 1963-1968, (4 folders) (Box 182)
    - Current, 1966-1967 (Box 182)
    - Contracts, budget, 1964-1967 (Box 182)
    - Correspondence, publicity, 1966-1967 (Box 182)
    - Comparative programs, 1965-1967 (Box 182)
    - National arts center study I-III, 1966; (3 folders) (Box 182)
  - West European studies, 1965-1968; (3 folders) (Box 182)
  - West Indies, University of, 1962-1966 (Box 182)
  - West Virginia, 1962-1966 (Box 182)
  - Western interstate commission for higher education, 1962-1968 (Box 182)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation, 1967 (Box 182)
  - Wh, 1964-1966 (Box 183)
  - Whi, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wi, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wil, 1964-1968 (Box 183)
  - Will, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wilm, 1963-1964 (Box 183)
  - Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, Woodrow, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 183)
  - Wim, 1967 (Box 183)
  - Winona Village Housing operating statements, 1962-1963 (Box 183)
  - Winstead, Nash N. (Box 183)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 183)
    - Ellis L. Phillips Foundation Intern in Adminstration (Box 183)
  - Wir, 1966 (Box 183)
  - Wisconsin, University of (Box 183)
    - Madison, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 183)
    - Superior, 1964-1968; (3 folders) (Box 183)
    - Graduate School of Banking, 1966 (Box 183)
  - Wiseley, William Clement, 1966 (Box 183)
  - Wit, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - W, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wo, 1964-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wolf, 1962-1966 (Box 183)
  - Women's education, 1968 (Box 183)
  - Work study program, 1965-1968 (Box 183)
  - Woo, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - Wool, 1962-1968 (Box 183)
  - World's fair, 1964-1966; (4 folders) (Box 183)
  - Wr, 1964-1968 (Box 184)
  - Writers' conference, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 184)
  - Wu, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
  - X-Y, 1962-1968 (Box 184)
  - Xerox, 1964-1967; (3 folders) (Box 184)
  - Yale University, 1962-1968; (4 folders) (Box 184)
  - Yo, 1962-1968 (Box 184)
  - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1962-1968; (7 folders) (Box 184)
  - Young Socialist Alliance Controversy (YSA) (Box 184)
    - 1965, (2 folders) (Box 184)
    - Indiana Supreme Court opinion, January 25, 1965 (Box 184)
    - Correspondence, from, July 1963 (Box 184)
    - 1962-1963, (2 folders) (Box 184)
    - Neugeboren article, 1963 (Box 184)
    - Russian lectures, 1963 (Box 184)
    - News clippings (Box 184)
      - Indiana Daily Student, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
      - Indianapolis News, 1963 (Box 184)
      - Indianapolis Star, 1963 (Box 184)
      - Indianapolis Times, 1963 (Box 184)
      - Louisville Courier-Journal, 1963 (Box 184)
      - Other sources, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
      - Extra articles, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
      - Daily Herald, 1963-1964 (Box 184)
    - Correspondence to, June 1963 (Box 184)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1962-1968; (5 folders) (Box 184)
  - Yugoslav program, 1962-1968; (6 folders) (Box 184)
  - Z, 1962-1968 (Box 185)
  - Zoology, 1962-1964 (Box 185)
  - Zi, 1962-1968 (Box 185)
  - International Affairs center administration board minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 185)
  - International Programs of American Universities, 1967 (Box 185)
  - Graduate exchange program, Chinese University, Hong Kong, 1966-1967 (Box 185)
  - Halls of residence, 1966 (Box 185)
  - Human experimentation, 1966 (Box 185)
  - Human relations area files, 1963-1964 (Box 185)
  - IU jazz band, 1966 (Box 185)
  - National science foundation, cyclotron, 1966-1968 (Box 185)